<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rdf:RDF
	xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
>
<channel rdf:about="http://planet.du.zoomquiet.us/">
	<title>Planet DebugUself</title>
	<link>http://planet.du.zoomquiet.us/</link>
	<description>Planet DebugUself - http://planet.du.zoomquiet.us/</description>

	<items>
		<rdf:Seq>
			<rdf:li rdf:resource="http://localhost:1313/post/20180422-magical-should-thinking/" />
			<rdf:li rdf:resource="http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/" />
			<rdf:li rdf:resource="http://liguanghe.github.io/2018/04/17/TimeReport2018/" />
		</rdf:Seq>
	</items>
</channel>

<item rdf:about="http://localhost:1313/post/20180422-magical-should-thinking/">
	<title>zoejane: Learn to Say Goodbye to Magical Should Thinking</title>
	<link>http://localhost:1313/post/20180422-magical-should-thinking/</link>
	<content:encoded>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you constantly tell yourself you should be better, or should be doing more, or should magically know how to do things without practice, then you’re going about it all wrong. I work crazy hard at the things I want to be good at and I don’t expect to be an expert in them without a lot of work, and possibly never in my lifetime. I don’t tell myself I should be better at painting. I just paint, and then figure out how I can do better the next time. Too often though I see people who, despite not investing any time in learning to code, have this unrealistic idea that they should be better at it. They should just know how to code a small project from nothing.
- &lt;a href=&quot;https://forum.learncodethehardway.com/t/help-wanted-on-showing-up-everyday/60/4&quot;&gt;Zed Shaw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the &amp;lsquo;Magical Should Thinking&amp;rsquo; is just what I did for a long time. And that&amp;rsquo;s the reason why I always feel upset when I learning programming or music or just anything else.
I thought I should do better, I should do more. But actually, I can&amp;rsquo;t make it. I blame myself, I think maybe I could not make it forever, then I just wanna give up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what I could learn from Zed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Just do it, just practice, keep on practicing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on how I can do better the next time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even if I make something that&amp;rsquo;s not good, that&amp;rsquo;s ok. I just need more practice. it&amp;rsquo;s just an opportunity that I could improve myself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What could I practice now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I try to start to write my English blog now. Even if seems hard to me, but I will try. Try to write down some simple sentences, try to write down my thoughts.
At first, I could only write down one simple paragraph this morning. But in the evening, I never thought I could write down so many words.
I even searched for some podcasts to improve my English this afternoon and maybe I will write some notes on learning English, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I worried about I could not write a good English blog, then I would not try to take the tiny step to write down my first paragraph, then all these things will not happen.
I am happy to experience that, if I start to do it, I could find more joy and interesting changes that I never thought before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanna celebrate my first start.
And I am happy that I could meet Zed Shaw, he gave me a lot of encouragement and inspiration.
I will try to practice more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;changelog&quot;&gt;Changelog&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20180422 zoejane update - 31 mins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20180422 zoejane init first paragraph - 20 mins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded>
	<dc:date>2018-04-22T03:23:18+00:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/">
	<title>zoejane: Hello World</title>
	<link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/</link>
	<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hello world!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
	<dc:date>2018-04-22T02:45:48+00:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://liguanghe.github.io/2018/04/17/TimeReport2018/">
	<title>li guang he</title>
	<link>http://liguanghe.github.io/2018/04/17/TimeReport2018/</link>
	<content:encoded>Bokeh Plot</content:encoded>
	<dc:date>2018-04-17T02:53:41+00:00</dc:date>
</item>

</rdf:RDF>
